<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" >
  <generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.0">Jekyll</generator>
  <link href="/author/naren/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" />
  <link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" />
  <updated>2023-07-15T09:55:25+00:00</updated>
  <id>/author/naren/feed.xml</id>

  
  
  

  
    <title type="html">Hello, I’m Naren 👋 | </title>
  

  
    <subtitle>Anecdotes of my Thoughts, Learnings, and Ideas. &lt;/br&gt; (mostly on marketing and building products)</subtitle>
  

  

  
    
      
    
  

  
  

  
    <entry>
      <title type="html">Welcome to Ghost</title>
      <link href="/welcome" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to Ghost" />
      <published>2017-07-27T10:00:00+00:00</published>
      <updated>2017-07-27T10:00:00+00:00</updated>
      <id>/welcome</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="/welcome">&lt;p&gt;Hey! Welcome to Ghost, it’s great to have you :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We know that first impressions are important, so we’ve populated your new site with some initial &lt;strong&gt;Getting Started&lt;/strong&gt; posts that will help you get familiar with everything in no time. This is the first one!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;there-are-a-few-things-that-you-should-know-up-front&quot;&gt;There are a few things that you should know up-front:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ghost is designed for ambitious, professional publishers who want to actively build a business around their content. That’s who it works best for. If you’re using Ghost for some other purpose, that’s fine too - but it might not be the best choice for you.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The entire platform can be modified and customized to suit your needs, which is very powerful, but doing so &lt;strong&gt;does&lt;/strong&gt; require some knowledge of code. Ghost is not necessarily a good platform for beginners or people who just want a simple personal blog.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;For the best experience we recommend downloading the Ghost Desktop App for your computer, which is the best way to access your Ghost site on a desktop device.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ghost is made by an independent non-profit organisation called the Ghost Foundation. We are 100% self funded by revenue from our &lt;a href=&quot;https://ghost.org/pricing&quot;&gt;Ghost(Pro)&lt;/a&gt; service, and every penny we make is re-invested into funding further development of free, open source technology for modern journalism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main thing you’ll want to read about next is probably: &lt;a href=&quot;https://demo.ghost.io/the-editor/&quot;&gt;the Ghost editor&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you’re done reading, you can simply delete the default &lt;strong&gt;Ghost&lt;/strong&gt; user from your team to remove all of these introductory posts!&lt;/p&gt;</content>

      
      
      
      
      

      <author>
          <name>Naren Sundar</name>
        
        
      </author>

      

      
        <category term="Getting started" />
      

      
        <summary type="html">Hey! Welcome to Ghost, it’s great to have you :)</summary>
      

      
      
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <title type="html">Making your site private</title>
      <link href="/private-sites" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Making your site private" />
      <published>2017-07-27T06:00:00+00:00</published>
      <updated>2017-07-27T06:00:00+00:00</updated>
      <id>/private-sites</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="/private-sites">&lt;p&gt;Sometimes you might want to put your site behind closed doors&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you've got a publication that you don't want the world to see yet because it's not ready to launch, you can hide your Ghost site behind a simple shared pass-phrase.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can toggle this preference on at the bottom of Ghost's General Settings&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://casper.ghost.org/v1.0.0/images/private.png&quot; alt=&quot;private&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ghost will give you a short, randomly generated pass-phrase which you can share with anyone who needs access to the site while you're working on it. While this setting is enabled, all search engine optimisation features will be switched off to help keep the site off the radar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Do remember though, this is &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; secure authentication. You shouldn't rely on this feature for protecting important private data. It's just a simple, shared pass-phrase for very basic privacy.&lt;/p&gt;</content>

      
      
      
      
      

      <author>
          <name>Naren Sundar</name>
        
        
      </author>

      

      
        <category term="Getting started" />
      

      
        <summary type="html">Sometimes you might want to put your site behind closed doors If you've got a publication that you don't want the world to see yet because it's not ready to launch, you can hide your Ghost site behind a simple shared pass-phrase. You can toggle this preference on at the bottom of Ghost's General Settings Ghost will give you a short, randomly generated pass-phrase which you can share with anyone who needs access to the site while you're working on it. While this setting is enabled, all search engine optimisation features will be switched off to help keep the site off the radar. Do remember though, this is not secure authentication. You shouldn't rely on this feature for protecting important private data. It's just a simple, shared pass-phrase for very basic privacy.</summary>
      

      
      
    </entry>
  
    <entry>
      <title type="html">The Businessman &amp;amp; The Fisherman</title>
      <link href="/the-businessman-and-fisherman" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Businessman &amp; The Fisherman" />
      <published>2014-08-12T10:18:00+00:00</published>
      <updated>2014-08-12T10:18:00+00:00</updated>
      <id>/the-businessman-and-fisherman</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="/the-businessman-and-fisherman">&lt;p&gt;An American businessman took a vacation to a small coastal Mexican village on doctor’s orders. Unable to sleep after an urgent phone call from the office the first morning, he walked out to the pier to clear his head. A small boat with just one fisherman had docked, and inside the boat were several large yellowfin tuna. The American complimented the Mexican on the quality of his fish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“How long did it take you to catch them?” the American asked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Only a little while,” the Mexican replied in surprisingly good English.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Why don’t you stay out longer and catch more fish?” the American then asked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I have enough to support my family and give a few to friends,” the Mexican said as he unloaded them into a basket.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“But… What do you do with the rest of your time?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Mexican looked up and smiled. “I sleep late, fish a little, play with my children, take a siesta with my wife, Julia, and stroll into the village each evening, where I sip wine and play guitar with my amigos. I have a full and busy life, señor.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The American laughed and stood tall. “Sir, I’m a Harvard M.B.A. and can help you. You should spend more time fishing, and with the proceeds, buy a bigger boat. In no time, you could buy several boats with the increased haul. Eventually, you would have a fleet of fishing boats.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He continued, “Instead of selling your catch to a middleman, you would sell directly to the consumers, eventually opening your own cannery. You would control the product, processing, and distribution. You would need to leave this small coastal fishing village, of course, and move to Mexico City, then to Los Angeles, and eventually to New York City, where you could run your expanded enterprise with proper management.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Mexican fisherman asked, “But, señor, how long will all this take?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To which the American replied, “15-20 years, 25 tops.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“But what then, señor?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The American laughed and said, “That’s the best part. When the time is right, you would announce an IPO and sell your company stock to the public and become very rich. You would make millions.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Millions señor? Then what?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Then you would retire and move to a small coastal fishing village, where you would sleep late, fish a little, play with your kids, take a siesta with your wife, and stroll in to the village in the evenings where you could sip wine and play your guitar with your amigos.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adapted from the “Anekdote zur Senkung der Arbeitsmoral” by &lt;strong&gt;Heinrich Böll&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An influential German write and Nobel Prize for Literature in 1972.&lt;/p&gt;</content>

      
      
      
      
      

      <author>
          <name>Naren Sundar</name>
        
        
      </author>

      

      
        <category term="fables" />
      

      
        <summary type="html">An American businessman took a vacation to a small coastal Mexican village on doctor’s orders. Unable to sleep after an urgent phone call from the office the first morning, he walked out to the pier to clear his head. A small boat with just one fisherman had docked, and inside the boat were several large yellowfin tuna. The American complimented the Mexican on the quality of his fish.</summary>
      

      
      
    </entry>
  
</feed>
